This is my powershell profile. I host it on git so I can easily move my profile between computers and share my set-up.

You can either browse through and copy individual functions that you want.

To set up something similar for your profile, check out my answer on Stackoverflow to learn how to move your default profile location:

https://stackoverflow.com/questions/5095509/is-it-possible-to-change-the-default-value-of-profile-to-a-new-value/50557964#50557964